I think it's pure perfection.
I think
We are getting more and more in sync.
Open.
Don't move from this angle.
Look forward.
Why?
You take such good pictures for them.
What is this?
Don't I take good pictures of you?
Too much.
More cheese is better.
He asked me to wipe it for him.
Can you wipe mine too?
Okay?
Why are you wiping it so perfunctorily?
Boys these days
Are getting harder to discipline.
Hurry up.
I want pizza.
You look like pizza.
Ke Yu.
What?
I want coffee.
I've ordered it for you.
It'll be here soon.
Really?
How did you know I wanted coffee?
I'm just that amazing.
Wait a moment.
How do I...
I'm really scared.
Aren't I right here?
Now I'm the elder sister.
You are the younger brother.
Okay.
Then call me sister.
Sister.
Do you think it's cute
Or am I cute?
You are cuter.
It's going to fall off.
It's so sunny.
Summer Hut.
It's so beautiful.
That's a sunroom.
We can bask in the sun.
Hello.
It's really nice.
Hello, everyone.
Morning.
Long time no see.
Who's here?
Hello.
Long time no see.
Come inside.
Put your things inside.
Let's go.
Living room.
I have prepared gifts for everyone.
You...
Do you want to guess what it is?
You didn't prepare your own little card, did you?
Do you think I'm like you?
Alright.
What I have prepared for everyone is a photo frame.
Photo frame.
It's a photo frame that can hold instant photos.
And I brought an instant camera.
We can take more photos.
The gifts we brought are the same.
What is yours?
Yours is also a photo frame?
I also brought a camera.
Photo paper, instant camera, and such.
I brought each of you a camera.
There are cameras,
And photo frames.
Then we can only keep taking pictures.
Here, I'll give you one.
Your gift.
Thank you.
This is a fridge magnet, isn't it?
It's a fridge magnet.
It's perfect.
How come there's more?
There are even words here.
Welcome to the Chixia Cabin, friends.
Two days and one night, only one purpose.
Find the most compatible partner.
Who exactly is that most compatible one?
Through daily interactions in the cabin,
You will feel and decide for yourselves.
When the prompt tone rings,
It's the moment for you to make your choice.
Find the most compatible partner.
Feels like a lot of fun.
Dear friends,
The partner self-recommendation session starts now.
Start the introduction.
Introduce yourself.
Then I'll go first.
You go.
I'm just a person from Beijing.
I definitely won't vote for this one.
Next one.
I can bring you energy.
Because I think today
I've brought watermelon and food.
I think I can bring you joy.
He's afraid that others can't tell
He's from Beijing.
But where are you really from?
I'm from Hunan.
He's from Hunan.
Really?
Isn't this your hometown?
Right.
So this is my hometown, you know?
I just have a lot of skills.
For example,
I can cook.
And I can do most sports.
And I also have a driver's license.
You have a driver's license?
This is actually not bad.
Indeed.
As for me,
I'm purely and completely
A service-oriented good partner.
If you choose me as the popular partner,
I will definitely serve you well.
Although I don't do much work,
But...
Although you don't do much work...
I might not do much work,
But I will definitely
Do my utmost
To serve you all well.
I am
A "princess".
I am...
I am an all-around partner.
I can do everything.
I can also cook.
And I cook especially well.
And then I also can...
I also have a service-oriented personality.
Okay.
I can...
She has covered you.
And she has also covered me.
She has more functions than me.
She is the professional version.
I can also take good care of everyone.
And I'm also half a Hunanese.
I don't believe it.
What language is this?
Hunanese.
I can't understand at all.
He is a fake Hunanese.
Alright, fake Hunanese.
I am the real Hunanese.
I'm familiar with this.
Who votes for me?
I absolutely won't.
I absolutely won't vote.
Just kidding.
Well,
Let's all improvise a bit.
Let's see who is more like a partner with whom.
Okay.
What to act?
Come on.
AI generated a script, right, bro?
Well done.
Lu Xijiao, your lines are...
Please use the "domineering CEO" style
To perform this famous scene of yours.
Please use what, the "domineering CEO" style?
Right.
Come on.
Do it now.
We're using that kind of short play.
That kind of "domineering CEO" style.
Right.
I am now the "domineering CEO".
Zhou Wanniao, let me tell you.
Right.
The matter back then.
♪Tear it apart and crush it♪
Right.
♪It's all because you let me down♪
Right, that's the feeling.
Come and feel it, come on.
What role am I?
You are a girl from Guangzhou.
Guangzhou.
A young lady who can't speak Cantonese well.
Speak fake Cantonese.
Right.
Come on, say it once.
Many things...
Many things, I have forgotten.
Got it.
Okay, come on.
You've forgotten too, right?
Next line.
Why doesn't this actor remember the lines?
Sorry.
You've lied to me a hundred times.
Okay.
As long as you say you love me once,
I will forgive you.
Okay. Come on.
What should I say?
You don't have to say anything.
Silence
Is tonight's Cambridge.
Okay. Come on.
Three, two, one.
When Beijing meets Guangzhou,
What kind of story will happen? Come on.
The promotion video of "Brilliant Summer".
Scene one, take one, action.
Zhou Wan.
I'm telling you, about that thing back then,
No matter how I think about it,
You are the only one who is sorry to me.
Do you know that?
I have forgotten a lot of things.
You'd better forget it, too.
Although you have lied to me a hundred times,
As long as you lie to me...
No.
But...
But as long as you say you love me once,
I'll forgive you.
Cut.
Keep the mood, quickly.
Forgive him or not?
Tears burst out, quickly.
The actor has no mood.
No.
Which actor has no mood?
Lu Xijiao.
Director.
I need to change.
I'm changing my character setting.
I want to speak
Chinese Hong Kong plastic Mandarin.
Okay.
I think you need to change your emotions.
Later, he says he wants you to forget him.
You can't be aggressive anymore.
Okay, it's very much this...
Contrast.
Right.
At this moment,
You are Tony Leung.
At this moment, you are Maggie Cheung.
I am Maggie Cheung.
I will bring out all my acting skills.
Alright, come on.
Three, two, one.
Scorching Summer promotional video, shot one, take one.
Action!
Zhou Wan, let me tell you about what happened back then.
♪Tear it apart and crush it♪
♪All that remains is you saying you're sorry♪
Actually,
I've already forgotten.
So please,
Just forget it too.
Okay?
Even if you lie to me a hundred times,
As long as you say you love me once,
I'll forgive you.
Lu Xijiao.
I can't do it, director.
I quit.
Lu Xijiao.
Keep going.
I can't do it.
What are you doing?
Get up.
I tripped over my dress.
Good.
Wait.
I think it's great.
I want to cross-dress.
I want to play Lu Xijiao.
You play Zhou Wan.
Okay.
Come on.
Is Zhou Wan that?
This is my version.
Okay.
I like it.
Come on, I'm ready.
Come on.
Ready, three, two, one.
Go.
Zhou Wan.
♪The past is♪
♪torn apart and broken♪
♪You owe me an apology♪
Lu Xijiao.
What's wrong with Zhou Wan?
Her vocal cords are at home.
Lu Xijiao.
Yes.
That's the feeling, yes.
I've already forgotten.
You should forget it too.
Zhou Wan.
As long as you are...
Why don't you give me a shot?
I'm sorry.
When I was ready to perform...
Come on.
Three, two, one, go.
Zhou Wan.
As long as you say you love me once,
I will forgive you.
Forgive him.
I'm an audience, forgive him.
This is the veteran artist.
I just say Zhou Wan...
Has this version been elevated, bro?
It's so good.
Actually, the two of us,
When we were filming this drama,
Always like this.
Right.
We were like this on set.
Really?
Yes.
When we were rehearsing,
We always played it backwards.
When the filming was almost over,
I was able to
Predict some scenes.
I knew how she would act.
Me too.
I even told him,
You would look more like a man.
A real man, bro.
A real man is coming.
The promotion video of "Summer Heat" is completed.
Come on.
Wait a moment.
Here's the thing.
Actually, I have some
Ideas for my creation.
Okay.
Because
The original drama just now
Was a scene
Performed by me and Zhou Wan.
Right.
So now,
I just hope...
For example,
If Ke Chun plays Lu Xijiao,
What version would it be?
Come on, where are you from?
Where?
Sichuan.
Sichuan person, okay.
What's your surname?
What surname?
You are Lu Xijiao.
Or do you want to play Zhou Wan?
Then you must play Zhou Wan.
Because I look at this face.
I can't speak.
Let me go.
He speaks so badly.
Let's each do it once.
Right.
Should he go next?
Come on.
I'll speak Henan dialect.
No problem, okay.
After all, it's a dialect.
Are you ready?
Three, two, one, start.
Zhou Wan.
I finally found you.
As for what happened back then,
It was all your fault.
You're the one who wronged me.
I've already
Forgotten everything.
You should forget it too.
Forget it?
Just say you love me,
And I'll forgive you.
Who do you think you are?
I don't believe you.
Is that okay, director?
Yes.
Thank you, director.
Very good.
Right.
It's your turn.
Don't try to run.
That's enough.
Okay, no.
Do an oily version.
I'll hold the camera this time.
Okay, come on.
Start filming.
Zhou Wan.
The matter back then
Was thoroughly analyzed.
Cue.
It was only you.
Sorry, I...
You're the only one who's sorry.
Cue.
Her lines.
Sorry.
I've
Forgotten everything.
You should
As soon as possible.
I forgot.
Very good.
From the eye acting just now,
I felt a kind of
Deep farewell.
I feel I didn't perform well.
Enough, keep the mood in your heart.
Applause for "Summer".
Come on, three, two, one.
Okay.
I have a general understanding.
Then let's see your performance.
Okay.
It's lunchtime.
Who can cook?
We both can.
I want to drink chicken soup.
There is a chicken coop in the yard.
Kill a chicken.
Do you want to drink chicken soup, bro?
If you want to drink chicken soup, you go.
You go catch it.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Go.
You want to catch a chicken, right?
Aren't you afraid of chickens?
I won't catch it.
Bag.
Bao,
Cover your back.
Didn't you wear the waist bag?
No, I feel uncomfortable.
I didn't either.
You tied it on your leg.
No, I also hung it.
But I can cover it like this.
Bro,
I think
You should
To experience it.
No.
Let's go.
Don't.
It's okay.
Bro.
Wait. I'm here.
Okay. I can do it.
You can do it.
Come on.
I'll observe and learn, okay?
Actually, it's very cute.
Who? You mean Zhou Keyu?
We need to catch a bigger chicken.
What about it?
I'll get you a chicken cage now.
Okay, come in first.
I won't go in, no.
It's you.
Yeah, this one.
This one.
Then
We'll seal it up.
Otherwise, it will fly out.
It's really scary.
Okay.
We're here with the chicken cage.
Did you catch it?
No.
We didn't catch any.
What?
Look, it's very cute.
Go away.
Zhou Keyu.
Touch it.
Come on.
Do we still need to tie it up?
Just put it in directly, right?
No need to tie it up.
Ke Chun, you're done for.
Today, I won't
Let you eat.
I'll tell Ke Yu about it later.
I'm sorry.
I'll let Ke Yu punish you.
Ke Yu.
Coming.
It's safe now. It's very safe now.
They have finished.
They tied the ropes.
Are they done?
Yeah.
I'm not afraid of it.
You know?
I'm afraid of it getting close to me.
I
Like the distance.
Come on, let's start.
What should we do first?
Then let's do this.
Let's prepare the ingredients first.
Then put them aside.
Okay.
That's right.
Cut some for me.
This kind of thin one.
Okay.
Ke Yu, can you cut tomatoes?
Give it to me.
Ke Chun.
Can you help me cut more garlic?
Okay, how many do you need?
Seven or eight.
Seven or eight?
Yes.
Okay, no problem.
Okay.
I am 'Chef Bao En'.
Is this thin enough?
Each slice.
Or...
Cut it in the middle.
I want vertical strips.
Okay.
I'm simply
Good at smashing garlic.
You know?
Look, it's frozen.
It needs to be thawed.
Is there hot water?
Adjust the heat.
You go first.
It's your specialty.
Don't talk about this small place.
It's quite beautiful when you look up.
Isn't it?
That's what I'm saying.
Cooking here is very healing.
This is my dream home.
Dream home.
I want to
Spend my retirement in a place like this,
Growing vegetables and such.
It popped.
Open this a bit wider.
Stop doing that.
It's okay.
I just feel like
I can't catch my breath.
I'll open this a bit wider.
Thank you.
Give me the celery.
Give me the chili pepper.
Here.
Be nervous.
It looks good.
Give me the dried tofu.
Dried tofu.
How does it look?
It's very common. Good.
It's very Hunan.
I just feel hot.
Is it hot?
My hands are burning.
I have a fan here.
Great.
The wok is too hot.
Thank you.
Ke Yu is so thoughtful.
Why don't I have a fan?
I don't have one either.
Why don't I have one?
You have one.
The late fan is cheaper than grass.
It's almost done.
The surface is golden.
Come on, I put them all here, chef.
Thank you.
It's stuck.
Oh, no. I need a shovel.
Hold it.
Actually, you look like
Someone who can cook.
Actually, I can cook.
You can't cook.
Actually, I really can cook.
I really can cook.
What dish can you cook?
I can cook anything.
For example?
I can make everything you can make.
Really?
You look like you can't cook. You're bluffing.
You just said I look like I can cook.
Now you say I look like I can't cook.
Why are you so contradictory?
You...
I'm teasing you.
Give me the soy sauce.
Put it here. Yeah.
Put in a handful of dried chili peppers.
Okay.
So spicy.
This is the charm of Hunan cuisine.
Don't try this. Try the chicken wings.
It's hot.
How is it?
It's okay.
Look at the crystal clear chicken wings.
This looks pretty good.
To be honest.
Now,
The dishes of "Master Chef Bao"
Are all done.
Guard my chicken wings.
Put it down.
Yeah.
Push it down.
It's okay.
Okay.
It won't be touched.
Braised pork.
The braised pork I made is super delicious.
Right?
This is ready.
This dish is really beautiful.
It's really good-looking.
It's a bit like the kind you'd find in a restaurant.
I think we are
Kitchen geniuses.
Will it be tasty?
Very.
It looks scary.
Give it to me.
Okay.
This is prepared for you.
Super.
Bro.
This dish is so authentic.
Let's go, start eating.
I can't wait.
Let's start.
Worthy of applause.
That's amazing.
It's really amazing.
It's amazing that
We can cook in this day.
It's not easy.
And the veteran artist insists on hand washing.
Yes.
Let's dig in.
Dig in.
Cheers.
I can't wait.
I'm starving.
Let's eat.
I'll have a chicken wing first.
I want chicken wings too.
Hunan-style chicken wings.
Try this.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
Which one?
This one is the best.
Chicken wings.
Chicken wings?
The chicken wings should have been stewed a little longer.
I think this one
Is the most suitable in terms of saltiness.
You guys try this one.
Try this one.
Bro.
I'll do it myself.
I'll do it myself later.
I don't want it.
She's been rejected.
Is it delicious?
It's very tasty.
He loves this.
Really?
It's really tasty.
When we were filming 'Scorching Summer',
We were really happy.
That was the happiest I've ever been on a set.
Indeed.
Yes.
Really.
It feels like
It's hard to find another
Such crew.
You mean that place.
That place is good.
The place is particularly good.
And comfortable.
Comfortable, and then
The people are also good.
Everyone gets along well.
The director is also very good.
He's amiable.
The producer is also nice.
Everyone is very harmonious.
Really.
Let's talk about
The first time
We met in the crew.
Your first impression of me.
The first time I saw you
Was when we were
Fighting in the rental house.
That was our first scene.
The first day I saw you.
That was also your first scene.
My first impression of you.
Let me tell you.
We were in the makeup car.
You were indeed quite noisy.
I think the first impression
Is the same as the impression I have of you now.
Actually, you
Have always been true to yourself.
Yeah, and you're quite real.
So,
What about Ke Yu?
I thought you were
At least
Three meters tall.
No.
The first time...
I remember telling you
That I thought
You were very tall.
But it turns out he's just average.
He's just average?
I don't even want to talk about mine.
Let me tell you this.
I don't know why.
Is it because
You were dressed too casually that day?
Right?
You were also dressed
Very casually that day.
We were reading around at that time.
We were dressed in all black.
Then, as we kept filming, I realized...
I was thinking,
Why is he getting taller day by day?
Taller and taller every day.
He's growing.
He's still growing.
My first impression,
Actually, I think he's quite...
Well,
What's that called?
He doesn't look
Very smart,
But he is actually very smart.
Because he...
He usually looks
Like a fool.
Am I a fool?
If you don't know him,
And don't understand him...
Bro.
I'm not a fool, right?
If you don't know him,
You would think he's not smart.
But later you would find
He's really smart.
Because I wasn't the one who started
The first drama,
I thought you two
Would be really aloof.
But I found you weren't.
And I found Bao really loves laughing.
Bao loves laughing.
Yeah, your first impression of me.
Yeah, just love to laugh.
Right.
And it's been a while
Since we last met.
Yesterday's first impression
Was that you're very smart.
Because I saw your candid shots.
Wearing glasses.
Really?
Do I look good?
Very smart.
Yes, it looks good.
Thank you.
Thank you for affirming my outfit.
Actually, I am still a
"trendsetter".
I am also a fashion blogger.
She's always showing off, oh my.
So beautiful.
I'm full.
What can we do now that we're full?
Partner, partner.
Good partner.
Who is my good partner?
The voting starts now.
Go check the bulletin board quickly.
Vote.
I vote for you.
I also vote for you.
Oh my.
I vote for you.
No.
If you two vote like this,
We won't be able to choose anyone.
Bro.
The one with the highest votes
The one with the highest number of votes
Is the most popular partner.
If you vote like this, it will be a tie.
Where to check?
The bulletin board.
Voting starts.
Please collect
Your own profile picture cards.
Decide the order on your own.
Proceed to the function room in turn.
Based on everyone's lunch performance,
Put the head portrait cards
Into the box of the desired partner.
To put it plainly,
This part, my family,
Is not controversial, right?
What's the controversy?
Who made the best food?
The most appetizing food?
What do you guys think?
This girl...
I think this girl
Is good at cooking.
Who is she?
Please say her name loudly.
I think that bead is also good.
Functional room, functional room.
That's the place.
Just over there.
I'll go first.
Can't we go together?
Of course not.
This is the anonymous part.
It's very shy, you know?
Shy.
I think, whether in the acting part
Or the cooking part,
Bao is the most perfect partner in my heart.
I don't need to know
Who she chose.
I don't need to know.
I respect her choice.
Okay.
I decide to vote for
Ke Yu.
There's really no choice.
I just want to vote for him/her.
Okay, friends.
Next,
We are going to announce
A popular partner for this round.
So if things go as expected,
This popular partner
Is most likely
The most handsome me.
Partner, good partner.
♪The scorching summer is as hot as 108 degrees♪
♪Bao Shangen is my good partner♪
Who?
Me.
Bao Shangen is my...
Bao Shangen is my good partner.
I'm speechless.
It's really delicious.
Let me see what it says.
Popular partner, take a seat.
Invite whoever you want.
What is this?
Okay, read it.
Popular partner, take a seat.
Invite whoever you want.
Always on call.
No nagging.
One hundred percent cooperation.
Never dodge.
Exclusive benefits have landed.
Go to the bulletin board to collect.
Go.
Collect at the bulletin board.
Partner, partner, good partner.
Who is my good partner?
You recorded it, right?
Just now.
This one?
Summoning artifact usage rules.
I can
Designate someone to be on call.
The designated person must
Cooperate one hundred percent.
Be on call.
To put it plainly,
I've never liked to cooperate with others since I was young.
I'm particularly hard to deal with.
I'm the hardest to deal with, my friend.
How can you call me and I won't come?
He is provoking you.
You are the hardest to deal with.
Then we can only use him.
Then it can only be you.
I...
Let me tell you.
You must be on call at all times
And cooperate one hundred percent.
I'll choose you.
Okay.
In the following time,
It is until he...
Until I'm old, right?
It's for this lifetime.
This lifetime, I must
Be available on call.
You have to be available on call
For the rest of your life.
You have to.
You are like a "puppy".
This is cool.
To put it bluntly, a big brother.
This is really good.
Can you hear me?
No.
Bring me that watermelon.
No, what does it have to do with you?
You're ordering me around now.
Don't think about ordering
My man.
You can let Ke Yu hold it
And sleep with it.
No, bro.
I'm on call,
But I won't do everything you ask.
No.
You have to
Do everything I ask.
It says, "on call
And 100 percent cooperation." Okay.
Right, one hundred percent cooperation.
Okay, alright.
No problem, alright.
That day,
In that scene,
After I stabbed him
In the heart,
How did you feel?
I felt like I had lost him.
Goodbye forever.
Very serious.
It's that kind of
Emotional breakdown.
A bit heavy.
Suddenly it's deep conversation.
This is particularly good.
Today I think it's a good opportunity.
Just say it when you think of it.
We're getting more in sync.
To put it plainly, it's pure perfection.
Is there something on my face?
I'm stepping on him.
Go.
That's too high, isn't it?
Don't be afraid.
Hold on to me tightly.
This is so much fun.
I just want to play this kind of game.
Then you call me sister.
Sister.